cassiopessa.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | cassiopesa

**  Cassiopesa PRIVACY POLICY**

_Last updated:04/01/2015_

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes Cassiopesa (“we” or “us”) privacy practices with respect to your use of the Software (as such term is defined in the Cassiopesa ** ** EULA available here:[ cassiopesa.com/eula](http://cassiopesa.com/eula/ "Eula") (”Software EULA”). Please also see the Software EULA as your use of the Software is subject to the terms of this Privacy and the Software EULA. This Policy applies to our Software and does not apply to any third party services, websites, software and content that may be available as part of or linked to or from the Software.

By downloading and using the Software and/or by accepting this Policy and the Software EULA, you consent to our access, collection, use and/or disclosure of your information as described in this Policy.

**1.Information We Collect and Use**

1.1  Basic Information. When you use the Software, we may collect non-personal and technical information from you. This information may include your type of browser(s), your IP address and your computer operating system details. We collect and use this information to measure and improve the Software over time.

1.2  Search Related Information. As part of the Software you will be able to use features that provide you with the ability to conduct web searches. When you use these features we will collect information such as URL of the page containing the results of your search queries (“Search Generated Information”). The Search Generated Information may include your personal information such as your name, should you choose to search for results pertaining to it.

1.3  Cookies. As part of the Software we may use cookies and similar technologies to collect information such as your usage data and to improve the Software. A cookie is a small text file saved on your computer to help store preferences and other information that is used on webpages that you visit. We may use session cookies to better understand how you interact with the Software, to customize and improve the Software, and provide relevant advertisements and/or other services to you. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can change the settings of your browser at any time to delete/disable cookies. However, some features of the Software may not function properly if you disable cookies.

1.4  Third-Parties and Corporate Affiliates. We use a variety of third-party services as part of the Software, to provide you with certain features, and to help us understand and improve your use of the Software. These third-parties may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP address. You allow us to receive information about you if you use features of the Software that require you to log in to a third-party website or application such as Facebook or Google.

1.5  Information You Provide Us. When you contact us, we may collect your email address and the information we need to categorize your question, respond to it, and, if applicable, investigate any issues that you raise. We also use this information to track potential problems and customize our support responses to better serve you. We do not use this information for advertising purposes.

1.6  Additional features. We are always seeking to improve the Software. Therefore, we may introduce new features, some of which may result in the collection of additional information from you. If we start collecting additional types of personal information and materially change how we handle your information, we will modify this Policy and notify you in accordance with Section 6 (Changes to This Policy).

**2.Information Sharing and Disclosure**

2.1.We do not rent, sell, or share your personal information except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy or in the event that we have a good faith belief that disclosure is permitted by law or is reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with the law, a legal requirement or process, including without limitation, subpoenas, court orders, or other compulsory disclosures, or to establish, maintain or exercise our legal rights; (ii) enforce this Policy or the Software EULA; (iii) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities or violation of third party rights; or (iv) protect our rights. In addition, in the event that we undergo a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be one of the assets sold or transferred.

2.2.Service Providers. We may employ third parties to provide us with maintenance, analysis, audit, and development services with respect to the Software. We currently use (i) Google Analytics which uses the following sources for collecting information: (a) the HTTP request of the user; (b) browser/system information; and (c) first-party Cookies. These Cookies (as defined below) do not collect any personally identifiable information. You can read more about Google’s privacy Policy here: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>; (ii) desk.com by Salesforce, Inc. to provide us with personalized support services. You can read desk.com’s privacy policy at: <http://www.desk.com/privacy>; and (iii) Amazon Web Services, Inc. servers to process your Personal Information. You can read about the measures taken by Amazon to protect the security of their servers and your personal information at: <http://awsmedia.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/AWS_Security_Whitepaper.pdf>.

2.3.Partners; Corporate Affiliates. (i) We may share your information with our partners to prevent, detect and investigate fraud or other prohibited activities, facilitate dispute resolution such as chargebacks or refunds; and for other related purposes. These partners are bound by confidentiality obligations, and will only have limited access to your information as shall be necessary to resolve any of the above situations. (ii) We may also disclose your information to our corporate affiliates in order to help provide, understand, and improve the Software and our affiliates’ services, including without limitation, the delivery of ads, this means we may also internally combine information we have on you.

2.4.Data Transfer. We may transfer your information and process it on servers outside your country of residence.

**3.Security**

We have implemented security safeguards designed to protect your personal information in accordance with industry standards. We limit access to your information on our servers, and it is password-protected/encrypted. We also regularly monitor our servers for possible vulnerabilities and attacks. Nevertheless, as the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us. There is no guarantee that information on our servers may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of our safeguards.

**4.Modifying Your Personal Information**.

You have a right to request that we delete any of your personal information in our possession by sending us an email to:[ support@cassiopesa.com](http://support.cassiopesa.com/customer/portal/emails/new) We will generally delete your information within 30 days of receipt of your request.

**5.Our Policy Towards Children**

The Software is not intended and/or directed to persons under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that a child under that age has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information from our servers. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us at [support@cassiopesa.com](http://support.cassiopesa.com/customer/portal/emails/new)

**6.Changes to This Policy**

We may change this Policy from time to time. If we make changes, that are significant in our sole discretion, in the way we treat your personal information, or to the Policy, we will provide you with notice as part of the Software or by any other means. We will also post the revised Policy on the Software’s web site [_cassiopesa.com_](http://cassiopesa.com/)(“ **Site** ” _)_ , and will update the “Last Update” above. The most current version of this Policy will govern our use of your information and will always be available on the Site. Your continued use of the Software, following any change to this Policy, constitutes your complete and irrevocable acceptance of the updated Policy. If any changes to the Policy are not acceptable to you, you may uninstall the Software.

**7.Contact Information**

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, please contact us at [support@cassiopesa.com](http://support.cassiopesa.com/customer/portal/emails/new)
